import React from 'react'
let slogans = {
    title: "Slogans",
    questions: [
        {
            question: "This product is kid tested and mother approved",
            answers: ["Kix", "Wheaties", "Cp'n Crunch", "Cheerios"],
            correct: "Kix"
        },
        {
            question: "This company thinks that Life's Good",
            answers: ["Samsung", "Microsoft", "LG Electronics", "Panasonic"],
            correct: "LG Electronics"
        },
        {
            question: "This company says they're Trusted Everywhere",
            answers: ["American Express", "Mastercard", "Duracell Batteries", "Energizer", ],
            correct: "Duracell Batteries"
        },
        {
            question: "This company suggests that Maybe She's Born With It",
            answers: ["CoverGirl", "Clinique", "Maybelline", "Estee Lauder"],
            correct: "Maybelline"
        },
        {
            question: "This company says that we all need to Eat Mor Chikin",
            answers: ["KFC", "Chick-Fil-A", "Golden Chick", "Slim Chickens"],
            correct: "Chick-Fil-A"
        },
        {
            question: "This company is Everywhere You Want To Be",
            answers: ["American Express", "Visa", "Mastercard", "Discover"],
            correct: "Visa"
        },
        {
            question: "This company wants us to Gather 'Round the Good Stuff",
            answers: ["Pizza Hut", "Mazzio's", "Papa Johns", "Domino's"],
            correct: "Pizza Hut"
        },
        {
            question: "This company claims to Make Mouths Happy",
            answers: ["Dental Depot", "Skittles", "Gushers", "Twizzlers", ],
            correct: "Twizzlers"
        },
        {
            question: "This company claims its coffee is Good to the Last Drop",
            answers: ["Folgers", "Keefe", "Maxwell House", "Starbucks"],
            correct: "Maxwell House"
        },
        {
            question: "This branch of the military claims it's not just a job, it's an adventure!",
            answers: ["Army", "Navy", "Marines", "Coast Guard"],
            correct: "Navy"
        }
    ]
}

export default slogans